<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<defaultdata>
    <tbl_wiki_wikis>
        <id>init_1</id>
        <group_type>default</group_type>
        <group_id>1</group_id>
        <wiki_name>Default wiki</wiki_name>
        <wiki_description>The default wiki for the site</wiki_description>
        <wiki_visibility>1</wiki_visibility>
        <creator_id>1</creator_id>
        <date_created>2007-06-01 12:00:00</date_created>
    </tbl_wiki_wikis>
    <tbl_wiki_pages>
        <id>init_1</id>
        <wiki_id>init_1</wiki_id>
        <page_name>MainPage</page_name>
        <main_page>1</main_page>
        <page_summary>A brief overview of what a wiki is all about</page_summary>
        <page_content>[[toc]]
+++ What is a wiki
* A wiki is a website that allows visitors to add, remove, and edit content.
* This ease of interaction and operation makes a wiki an effective tool for mass collaborative authoring.
[MainPage Top]
----
+++ Characteristics
* A wiki enables documents to be written collaboratively, in a simple markup language using a web browser. A single page in a wiki is referred to as a "wiki page", while the entire body of pages, which are usually highly interconnected via hyperlinks, is "the wiki". A wiki is essentially a database for creating, browsing and searching information.
* A defining characteristic of wiki technology is the ease with which pages can be created and updated. Generally, there is no review before modifications are accepted.
[MainPage Top]
----
+++ Pages and editing
* The source format, sometimes known as "wikitext'", is augmented with a simplified markup language to indicate various structural and visual conventions. An often used example of one such convention is to start a line of text with an asterisk ("*") in order to mark it as an item in a bulleted list.
[MainPage Top]
----
+++ Linking and creating pages
* Wikis are a hypertext medium, with non-linear navigational structures. Each page typically contains a large number of links to other pages. Hierarchical navigation pages often exist in larger wikis, often a consequence of the original page creation process, but they do not have to be used. Links are created using a specific syntax, the so-called "link pattern".
* !CamelCase-based wikis are instantly recognizable because they have many links with names such as "!TableOfContents" and "!BeginnerQuestions".
[MainPage Top]
----
+++ Searching
* Most wikis offer at least a title search, and sometimes a full-text search.
[MainPage Top]
----
+++ Controlling changes
* History comparison reports highlight the changes between two revisions of a page. Wikis are generally designed with the philosophy of making it easy to correct mistakes, rather than making it difficult to make them. Thus, while wikis are very open, they provide a means to verify the validity of recent additions to the body of pages. The most prominent, on almost every wiki, is the "Recent Changes" page. A specific list numbering recent edits, or a list of all the edits made within a given time frame.
[MainPage Top]
----
+++ Reference
* [http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wiki http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wiki]
[MainPage Top]</page_content>
        <page_version>1</page_version>
        <version_comment>The default main page</version_comment>
        <page_status>1</page_status>
        <page_author_id>1</page_author_id>
        <date_created>2007-06-01 12:00:00</date_created>
    </tbl_wiki_pages>
    <tbl_wiki_links>
        <id>init_1</id>
        <wiki_name>MeatBall</wiki_name>
        <wiki_link>http://www.usemod.com/cgi-bin/mb.pl?%s</wiki_link>
    </tbl_wiki_links>
    <tbl_wiki_links>
        <id>init_2</id>
        <wiki_name>Wiki</wiki_name>
        <wiki_link>http://c2.com/cgi/wiki?%s</wiki_link>
    </tbl_wiki_links>
    <tbl_wiki_links>
        <id>init_3</id>
        <wiki_name>Wikipedia</wiki_name>
        <wiki_link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%s</wiki_link>
    </tbl_wiki_links>
</defaultdata>