<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- This file is a code generation template for Chisimba controller class setup -->

<chisimba_controller_skeleton>

<item name="startphp" type="control">
<description>
This is a parsecode that is used to create the start PHP
tag in the class file. It is necessary because starting PHP
uses XML reserved characters.
</description>
<code>{STARTPHP}
</code>
</item>

<item name="filecomment" type="comment">
<description>
This is a parsecode that is used to setup the page level
docblock comment.
</description>
<code>
/**
* 
* {MODULENAME}
*
* {MODULEDESCRIPTION}
* 
* PHP version 5
* 
* This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify 
* it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by 
* the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or 
* (at your option) any later version.
* This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, 
* but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of 
* MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the 
* GNU General Public License for more details.
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License 
* along with this program; if not, write to the 
* Free Software Foundation, Inc., 
* 59 Temple Place - Suite 330, Boston, MA  02111-1307, USA.
* 
* @category  Chisimba
* @package   {MODULECODE}
* @author    {AUTHOR} &lt;{EMAIL}&gt;
* @copyright 2007 AVOIR
* @license   http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt The GNU General Public License
* @version   CVS: $Id: controller_class_skeleton.xml 6961 2007-08-13 19:41:40Z dkeats $
* @link      http://avoir.uwc.ac.za
*/
</code>
</item>

<item name="security" type="control">
<description>
This item generates the security check that must be in all Chisimba
scripts to prevent the scripts from being run directly instead of
by the Chsimba engine.
</description>
<code> 
// security check - must be included in all scripts
if (!
/**
 * The $GLOBALS is an array used to control access to certain constants.
 * Here it is used to check if the file is opening in engine, if not it
 * stops the file from running.
 * 
 * @global entry point $GLOBALS['kewl_entry_point_run']
 * @name   $kewl_entry_point_run
 *         
 */
$GLOBALS['kewl_entry_point_run'])
{
        die("You cannot view this page directly");
}
// end security check
</code>
</item>

<item name="class" type="class">
<description>
This item sets up the skeleton of the controller class which
is then parsed to replace the parsecodes with the actual values
of the items.
</description>
<code>
/**
* 
* {MODULENAME}: 
* {MODULEDESCRIPTION}
*
* @author {AUTHOR}
* @category Chisimba
* @package {MODULECODE}
* @copyright {COPYRIGHT}
* @licence GNU/GPL
*
*/
class {CLASSNAME} extends controller

    {PROPERTIES}

    {METHODS}
    
    {SPECIALMETHODS}

}</code>
</item>

<item name="endphp" type="control">
<description>
This is a parsecode that is used to create the end PHP
tag in the class file. It is necessary because ending PHP
uses XML reserved characters.
</description>
<code>
{ENDPHP}</code>
</item>

</chisimba_controller_skeleton>