<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<defaultdata>
  <!-- Table tbl_stories -->
    <tbl_stories>
        <id>init_1</id>
        <category>prelogin</category>
        <isActive>1</isActive>
        <parentId>base</parentId>
        <language>en</language>
        <title>Chisimba default prelogin story</title>
        <abstract>This is the Chisimba main prelogin story</abstract>
        <mainText>&amp;nbsp;This is the default prelogin story. To edit this story, go to
site admin, and choose website stories, and edit this prelogin story.
Alternatively, you can delete this story and add one or more additional
stories to the prelogin category.</mainText>
        <dateCreated>2005-04-20 12:04:42</dateCreated>
        <creatorId>1</creatorId>
        <expirationDate>2025-04-21 00:00:00</expirationDate>
        <isSticky>1</isSticky>
        <modified>2006-07-12 11:59:29</modified>
        <dateModified>2005-04-20 12:04:12</dateModified>
        <modifierId>1</modifierId>
        <commentCount>0</commentCount>
    </tbl_stories>
    <tbl_stories>
        <id>init_2</id>
        <category>prelogin</category>
        <isActive>1</isActive>
        <parentId>base</parentId>
        <language>en</language>
        <title>Welcome to Chisimba</title>
        <abstract>Welcome to Chisimba, a rapid application development platform and next generation framework produced by the African Virtual Open Initiatives and Resources (AVOIR) project.</abstract>
        <mainText>Chisimba is an advanced rapid application development platform and next generation framework with features similar to common proprietary systems. It is free software (open source) released under the GNU GPL, and available for download via cvs checkout from http://cvs2.uwc.ac.za/ . Chisimba was developed based on several years of experience in software design and architecture at the University of the Western Cape and partner institutions using its predecessor KEWL.NextGen, and is under active development by a team of developers in 16 African higher education institutions.</mainText>
        <dateCreated>2005-04-20 12:04:35</dateCreated>
        <creatorId>1</creatorId>
        <expirationDate>2020-04-21 00:00:00</expirationDate>
        <isSticky>0</isSticky>
        <modified>2006-07-12 11:59:29</modified>
        <commentCount>0</commentCount>
    </tbl_stories>
    <tbl_stories>
        <id>init_3</id>
        <category>postlogin</category>
        <isActive>1</isActive>
        <parentId>base</parentId>
        <language>en</language>
        <title>You have successfully logged in to Chisimba</title>
        <abstract>You now have access to a rich set of features. You should really ask the system administrator for this site to change this message.</abstract>
        <mainText>You now have access to a rich set of features. If you are
looking for Kewl.Nextgen, please see http://avoir.uwc.ac.za/</mainText>
        <dateCreated>2005-04-20 12:04:34</dateCreated>
        <creatorId>1</creatorId>
        <expirationDate>2025-04-21 00:00:00</expirationDate>
        <isSticky>1</isSticky>
        <modified>2006-07-12 11:59:29</modified>
        <commentCount>0</commentCount>
    </tbl_stories>
</defaultdata>