<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
    
    <plugin name="tooltip">
        <description>
            Display a customized tooltip instead of the default one for every
            selected element.
        </description>
        <version ver="1.3.0">
            <file>jquery.tooltip.min.js</file>
            <css>jquery.tooltip.css</css>
            <min_core_version>1.2.2</min_core_version>
            <dependencies>
                <depends>bgiframe</depends>
                <depends>delegate</depends>
                <depends>dimensions</depends>
            </dependencies>
        </version>
    </plugin>
    
    <plugin name="bgiframe">
        <description>
            The background iframe (bgiframe) plugin provides a very small, quick
            and easy way to fix select form element z-index issue in Internet
            Explorer 6 so you don't have to worry about it. No matter the size,
            borders or position the bgiframe plugin can fix it. 
        </description>
        <version ver="2.1.2">
            <file>jquery.bgiframe.min.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.2.1</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="delegate">
        <description>
            This is a jquery plugin which handles event delegation.
        </description>
        <version ver="1.0.0">
            <file>jquery.delegate.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.2.1</min_core_version>
            <deprecated_from>1.4.2</deprecated_from>
        </version>
    </plugin>
    
    <plugin name="dimensions">
        <description>
            Dimensions extends jQuery to provide cross-browser methods for getting
            the position, inner width and height, outer width and height, and more.
        </description>
        <version ver="1.2.0">
            <file>jquery.dimensions.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.2.1</min_core_version>
            <deprecated_from>1.2.6</deprecated_from>
        </version>
    </plugin>
    
    <plugin name="validate">
        <description>
            This jQuery plugin makes simple clientside form validation trivial,
            while offering lots of option for customization. That makes a good
            choice if you’re building something new from scratch, but also when
            you’re trying to integrate it into an existing application with lots
            of existing markup. The plugin comes bundled with a useful set of
            validation methods, including URL and email validation, while providing
            an API to write your own methods. All bundled methods come with default
            error messages in english and translations into 36 locales.
        </description>
        <version ver="1.9.0">
            <file>jquery.validate.min.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.3.2</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="form">
        <description>
            The jQuery Form Plugin allows you to easily and unobtrusively upgrade
            HTML forms to use AJAX. The main methods, ajaxForm and ajaxSubmit, gather
            information from the form element to determine how to manage the submit
            process. Both of these methods support numerous options which allows you
            to have full control over how the data is submitted. Submitting a form
            with AJAX doesn't get any easier than this!
        </description>
        <version ver="3.0.8">
            <file>jquery.form.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.3.2</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>
    
    <plugin name="corner">
        <description>
            It's important to understand that this corner plugin is pulling off
            its magic by adding more elements to the page. Specifically, it adds
            div "strips" to the item to be cornered and sets a solid background
            color on these strips in order to hide the actual corners of the real item.
        </description>
        <version ver="2.1.2">
            <file>jquery.corner.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.3.2</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>
    
    <plugin name="flexigrid">
        <description>
            Lightweight but rich data grid with resizable columns and a scrolling
            data to match the headers, plus an ability to connect to an xml based
            data source using Ajax to load the content.
        </description>
        <version ver="1.1.0">
            <file>flexigrid.pack.js</file>
            <css>flexigrid.pack.css</css>
            <min_core_version>1.3.2</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="imagefit">
        <description>
            A jQuery plugin which scales images to fit their parent container.
            It is reliant on support for the CSS property max-width to prevent
            images from being enlarged beyond their native resolution. 
        </description>
        <version ver="0.2.0">
            <file>jquery.imagefit.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.2.1</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="livequery">
        <description>
            Live Query utilizes the power of jQuery selectors by binding events
            or firing callbacks for matched elements auto-magically, even after
            the page has been loaded and the DOM updated. 
        </description>
        <version ver="1.1.1">
            <file>jquery.livequery.min.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.3.0</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="pngfix">
        <description>
            This plugin will fix the missing PNG-Transparency in Windows Internet Explorer 5.5 and 6. 
        </description>
        <version ver="1.2.0">
            <file>jquery.pngFix.pack.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.3.0</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="oembed">
        <description>
            A simple jQuery plugin that uses OEmbed API to help displaying embedded 
            content (such as photos or videos) in your website. 
        </description>
        <version ver="1.1.0">
            <file>jquery.oembed.min.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.3.0</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

    <plugin name="flash">
        <description>
            A very lightweight jquery plugin that allows you to easily embed all
            sorts of flash content in a cross-browser compatible way without requiring
            a bulky dedicated library like swfobject.
        </description>
        <version ver="1.3.1">
            <file>jquery.flash.min.js</file>
            <min_core_version>1.2.1</min_core_version>
        </version>
    </plugin>

</plugins>