<data>
    <event 
        start="Jul 18, 1918"
        title="Mandela born"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
        Rolihlahla Mandela born in the small village of Qunu in the district of Mthatha, the Transkei capital on born July 18, 1918.His given name Rolihlahla means one who brings trouble upon himself.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1925"
        title="Named Nelson"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
        At seven years of age, Rolihlahla Mandela became the first member of his family to attend a school, where he was given the name "Nelson", after the British admiral Horatio Nelson, by a Methodist teacher.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1930"
        title="Father dies"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
        His father died in 1930, after which David Dalindyebo, then acting Paramount Chief of the tribe, became his guardian.
    </event>
    
    
    <event 
        start="1941"
        title="Move to Johannesburg"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_1.jpg">
    	Nelson Mandela arrives in Johannesburg. Like thousands of black South Africans, he left his rural village in search of a better life. 
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1942"
        title="Law clerk"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_2.jpg">
    	Mandela begins working in Johannesburg as a law clerk at the firm Witkin, Sidelsky &amp; Eidelman.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1944"
        title="Joins ANC"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_4.jpg">
    	Nelson Mandela joins the African National Congress (ANC). Nelson Mandela, Walter Sisulu, Oliver Tambo, and others form the ANC Youth League.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1948"
        title="Nationalists win elections"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	In 1948, the Afrikaner-dominated National Party won the elections in South African and brought its Apartheid policy of racial segregation into action in South Africa.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1952"
        title="Defiance campaign"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Mandela was prominent in the ANC's 1952 Defiance Campaign.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1952"
        title="Opens law firm"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_8.jpg">
    	Mandela, in partnership with Oliver Tambo, opens a law firm in Johannesburg, which defends blacks prosecuted under the strict new laws of apartheid.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1955"
        title="Congress of the People"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_10.jpg">
    	The Congress of the People took place in 1955, and adoption of the Freedom Charter provided the fundamental program of the anti-apartheid cause.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1956"
        end="1961"
        isDuration="true"
        title="Treason trial"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	1956-61 - Tried for treason, acquitted 1961
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1958"
        title="Verwoerd becomes Prime Minister"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_11.jpg">
    	H.F. Verwoerd becomes Prime Minister. His proposals to separate Blacks into independent states, or Bantustans, give him the title 'the chief architect of apartheid'.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1958"
        title="Marriage to Winnie"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_12.jpg">
    	Divorced from his first wife, Evelyn, Nelson Mandela marries Nomzamo Winnie Madikizela.
    </event>
    
    
    <event 
        start="Mar 21, 1960"
        title="Sharpeville Massacre"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	The Sharpeville massacre, also known as the Sharpeville shootings, occurred on March 21, 1960, when South African police opened fire on a crowd of black protesters. The confrontation occurred in the township of Sharpeville, in what is now Gauteng province.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Apr 1, 1960"
        title="UN Security Council sitting"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On April 1, 1960, the United Nations Security Council sat to "consider seriously the apartheid colonial oppression of the African people in South Africa".
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1961"
        title="Aquittal on treason"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Mandela was aquitted on the treason charges.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1961"
        title="Umkhonto we Sizwe"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	In 1961, Mandela became the leader of the ANC's armed wing, Umkhonto we Sizwe (translated as Spear of the Nation, also abbreviated as MK), which he co-founded.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Aug 5, 1962"
        title="Mandela Arrested"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On 5 August 1962, he was arrested after living on the run for seventeen months and was imprisoned in the Johannesburg Fort. 
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Oct 25, 1962"
        title="Sentence to prison"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/1_17.jpg">
    	On 25 October 1962, Mandela was sentenced to five years in prison.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Jul 11, 1963"
        title="ANC leaders arrested"
        image="http://localhost/chisimba/usrfiles/users/293062341/images/rivoniaraid-star.gif">
    	While Mandela was in prison, police arrested prominent ANC leaders on July 11, 1963, at Liliesleaf Farm, Rivonia, north of Johannesburg. 
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Apr 20, 1964"
        title="Rivonia trial defense case opens"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	In his statement from the dock at the opening of the defence case in the trial on 20 April 1964 at Pretoria Supreme Court, Mandela laid out the clarity of reasoning in the ANC's choice to use violence as a tactic.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="June 12, 1964"
        title="Mandela gets life sentence"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Mandela and all Rivonia trialists except Rusty Bernstein were found guilty, but they escaped the gallows and were sentenced to life imprisonment on 12 June 1964. Charges included involvement in planning armed action, in particular four charges of sabotage, which Mandela admitted to, and a conspiracy to help other countries invade South Africa, which Mandela denied.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1964"
        end="1990"
        isDuration="true"
        title="Prison"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Mandela spent 27 years in prison, most of them on Robben Island.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="June 12, 1964"
        title="Winnie arrested"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Winnie is arrested with twenty-one others and detained for five months. She is interrogated and tortured. 
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1970"
        title="Bantu Homelands Act"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	The government passes the Bantu Homelands Citizenship Act, which makes every black a citizen of a homeland, or a rural tribal area, rather than a citizen of South Africa.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Jun, 1976"
        title="Soweto uprising"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Soweto students hold a rally to protest mandatory instruction in Afrikaans, the language of the white rulers. Police open fire on the students killing 23 and injuring hundreds more. 
    </event>

    <event 
        start="May 19, 1977"
        title="Winnie banished"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/3_3.jpg">
    	Winnie Mandela is banished to Brandfort, a small, conservative Afrikaner town.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Sep 12, 1977"
        title="Biko murdered"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/3_4.jpg">
    	Steve Biko, founder of the Black Consiousness Movement, dies after being beat up by the police in detention.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1978"
        title="P.W. Both becomes president"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/4_2.jpg">
    	P.W. Botha succeeds B.J. Vorster as Prime Minister.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Jan 31, 1985"
        title="Botha's offer to Mandela"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	President P.W. Botha makes a conditional offer of release to Mandela.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Feb 10, 1985"
        title="Mandela replies to Both"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/4_3.jpg">
    	Mandela's youngest daughter, Zindzi, reads her father's reply to Botha's offer at a rally in Soweto. This is the first time in two decades that Mandela's words are heard by the public.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Jun 12, 1986"
        title="Secret talks"
        image="http://www.polity.org.za/html/people/images/mandela.jpg">
    	Mandela begins secret talks with the government, a decision made without consulting other leaders of the ANC organization.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="September 1989"
        title="De Klerk is President"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/4_6.jpg">
    	P.W. Botha resigned in July, and is succeeded by F.W. De Klerk as president of the Republic of South Africa.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="May 2, 1990"
        title="Mandela is free"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/4_7.jpg">
    	After 27 years of imprisonment, Mandela is released. He is free at last.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1993"
        title="Nobel peace prize"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif" 
        link="http://www.anc.org.za/ancdocs/speeches/nobelnrm.html">
    	Mandela won the Nobel Peace prize together with then President Frederik Willem de Klerk, for their work for the peaceful termination of the apartheid regime, and for laying the foundations for a new democratic South Africa.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="April, 1994"
        title="Democratic elections"
        image="http://www.radiodiaries.org/mandela/images/timeline/5_4.jpg">
    	For the first time in the country's history people of all races vote in democratic elections. Mandela is elected South Africa's first black president.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Jul 18, 1998"
        title="Marries Graca Machel"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On 18 July 1998, Mandela married Graca Machel, the widow of former Mozambique President Samora Machel.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1998"
        title="Children's fund announced"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif"
        link="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j7u_dL-z-UQ">
    	President Mandela announces the launch of the Nelson Mandela Children's Fund Canada (NMCF) at Toronto's SkyDome in 1998. <br />
    </event>
     
    
    <event 
        start="June, 1999"
        title="Retirement from public life"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Nelson Mandela retired from Public life in June 1999. He currently resides in his birth place - Qunu, Transkei.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="May 10, 2004"
        title="Ten years of Democracy"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Along with most of South Africa, Mandela celebrates 10 years of Democracy.
    </event>
    
    

    
</data>
