<data>
    <event 
        start="Jul 18, 1918"
        title="Mandela born"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
        Rolihlahla Mandela born in the small village of Qunu in the district of Mthatha, the Transkei capital on born July 18, 1918.His given name Rolihlahla means one who brings trouble upon himself.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1925"
        title="Named Nelson"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
        At seven years of age, Rolihlahla Mandela became the first member of his family to attend a school, where he was given the name "Nelson", after the British admiral Horatio Nelson, by a Methodist teacher.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1948"
        title="Nationalists win elections"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	In 1948, the Afrikaner-dominated National Party won the elections in South African and brought its Apartheid policy of racial segregation into action in South Africa.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1952"
        title="Defiance campaign"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Mandela was prominent in the ANC's 1952 Defiance Campaign.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1955"
        title="Congress of the People"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	The Congress of the People took place in 1955, and adoption of the Freedom Charter provided the fundamental program of the anti-apartheid cause.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Mar 21, 1960"
        title="Sharpeville Massacre"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	The Sharpeville massacre, also known as the Sharpeville shootings, occurred on March 21, 1960, when South African police opened fire on a crowd of black protesters. The confrontation occurred in the township of Sharpeville, in what is now Gauteng province.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Apr 1, 1960"
        title="UN Security Council sitting"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On April 1, 1960, the United Nations Security Council sat to "consider seriously the apartheid colonial oppression of the African people in South Africa".
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="1961"
        title="Umkhonto we Sizwe"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	In 1961, Mandela became the leader of the ANC's armed wing, Umkhonto we Sizwe (translated as Spear of the Nation, also abbreviated as MK), which he co-founded.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Aug 5, 1962"
        title="Mandela Arrested"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On 5 August 1962, he was arrested after living on the run for seventeen months and was imprisoned in the Johannesburg Fort. 
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Oct 25, 1962"
        title="Sentence to prison"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On 25 October 1962, Mandela was sentenced to five years in prison.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Jul 11, 1963"
        title="ANC leaders arrested"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	While Mandela was in prison, police arrested prominent ANC leaders on July 11, 1963, at Liliesleaf Farm, Rivonia, north of Johannesburg. 
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="Apr 20, 1964"
        title="Rivonia trial defense case opens"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	In his statement from the dock at the opening of the defence case in the trial on 20 April 1964 at Pretoria Supreme Court, Mandela laid out the clarity of reasoning in the ANC's choice to use violence as a tactic.
    </event>
    
    <event 
        start="June 12, 1964"
        title="Mandela gets life sentence"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	Mandela and all Rivonia trialists except Rusty Bernstein were found guilty, but they escaped the gallows and were sentenced to life imprisonment on 12 June 1964. Charges included involvement in planning armed action, in particular four charges of sabotage, which Mandela admitted to, and a conspiracy to help other countries invade South Africa, which Mandela denied.
    </event>

    <event 
        start="Jul 18, 1998"
        title="Marries Graca Machel"
        image="http://simile.mit.edu/images/csail-logo.gif">
    	On 18 July 1998, Mandela married Graca Machel, the widow of former Mozambique President Samora Machel.
    </event>

    
</data>
